https://shannon-muir.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY - Official Blog for the Animated Insights of Shannon Muir: Animation Writing and Production Pro and Author
Official Blog for the Animated Insights of Shannon Muir: Animation Writing and Production Pro and Author
An animation professional known for her desire to give forward to pros and fans alike, Shannon has expanded her reach to writing prose,
and showcasing those authors as well. Read interviews and guest posts from INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS, plus Shannon's own content.
Blog Guest Posts
Connect!
Blog Guest Posts
Connect!
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated: May 23, 2018
SHANNON MUIR’S OFFICIAL BLOG (including SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS) requires names and e-mails for sign-up in order to comment. This is only used to help determine whether or not you making legitimate, authentic comments or if the content comes from a spammer. It is used for no other purpose. Providing this information will be considered consent, as commenting on content is optional for accessing the site. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Please note that data is not shared with anyone. If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
All giveaways that appear on SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS are provided by third parties using Rafflecopter and are subject to Rafflecopter’s Terms and Conditions. Also note the information is being collected and used by the blog tour operators or authors who provide the Rafflecopter code to SHANNON MUIR’s OFFICIAL BLOG for SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS. Each post is clearly labeled as to who the providing entity is.
This site utilizes other third party social media applications including but not limited to Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter; your use of these plugins is subject to the Privacy Policy of the respective companies. Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
In regard to retention, if you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Cookies are also used at SHANNON MUIRS OFFICIAL BLOG (including SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS). This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymous tracking data to third party applications, such as Google Analytics. While user experience is generally improved using cookies, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org for  more information on how to disable them if you so choose.
If you leave a comment on this site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, the site will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
SHANNON MUIR’S OFFICIAL BLOG (including SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS) is run by Shannon Elise-Muir Broden, publishing as Shannon Muir. The mailing address for SHANNON MUIR’S OFFICIAL BLOG (including SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS) is PO Box 1505, Burbank, CA 91507, USA. The contact e-mail is shannon.muir@outlook.com.
If you wish your information to be removed and withdraw consent, please contact at the addresses listed above.  If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Tweet
SHANNON MUIR began working in animation on shows like EXTREME GHOSTBUSTERS and INVADER ZIM, worked on the virtual world NEOPETS/PETPET PARK, and now has credits writing for animation and short stories.FOLLOW SHANNON MUIR ON TWITTERTweets by Shannon_MuirCHECK OUT SHANNON MUIR’S ANIMATION4ALL ON TWITTERTweets by Animation4allCHECK OUT SHANNON MUIR’S INFINITE HOUSE OF BOOKS ON TWITTERTweets by InfiniteBooksCHECK OUT SHANNON MUIR’S THE PULP AND MYSTERY SHELF ON TWITTERTweets by mysteryshelfCHECK OUT FLYING GLORY AND THE HOUNDS OF GLORY, CO-CREATED BY SHANNON!Tweets by FlyingGloryFollow Shannon Muir, Author on Pinterest!
Shannon Muir, Author
Search
CHECK POST ARCHIVES BY MONTH CHECK POST ARCHIVES BY MONTH
Select Month
October 2020  (3)
September 2020  (15)
August 2020  (7)
July 2020  (17)
June 2020  (14)
May 2020  (14)
April 2020  (15)
March 2020  (18)
February 2020  (15)
January 2020  (18)
December 2019  (14)
November 2019  (12)
October 2019  (21)
September 2019  (17)
August 2019  (17)
July 2019  (18)
June 2019  (20)
May 2019  (19)
April 2019  (17)
March 2019  (16)
February 2019  (16)
January 2019  (23)
December 2018  (23)
November 2018  (18)
October 2018  (19)
September 2018  (16)
August 2018  (18)
July 2018  (19)
June 2018  (12)
May 2018  (14)
April 2018  (20)
March 2018  (17)
February 2018  (10)
January 2018  (14)
December 2017  (12)
November 2017  (17)
October 2017  (16)
September 2017  (13)
August 2017  (17)
July 2017  (19)
June 2017  (8)
May 2017  (16)
April 2017  (10)
March 2017  (10)
February 2017  (12)
January 2017  (12)
December 2016  (7)
November 2016  (24)
October 2016  (13)
September 2016  (12)
August 2016  (5)
July 2016  (10)
June 2016  (4)
May 2016  (5)
April 2016  (2)
March 2016  (2)
February 2016  (8)
January 2016  (1)
December 2015  (5)
November 2015  (5)
October 2015  (9)
September 2015  (5)
August 2015  (3)
July 2015  (8)
June 2015  (8)
May 2015  (3)
April 2015  (5)
March 2015  (6)
February 2015  (4)
November 2014  (1)
July 2014  (1)
June 2014  (2)
February 2014  (1)
January 2014  (1)
November 2013  (1)
October 2013  (1)
September 2013  (1)
August 2013  (1)
July 2013  (1)
June 2013  (1)
May 2013  (1)
February 2013  (1)
November 2012  (1)
September 2012  (1)
August 2012  (1)
June 2012  (1)
FIND OUT MORE ABOUT SHANNON’S WRITING AT SHANNON MUIR’S THE PULP AND MYSTERY SHELF!FIND OUT ABOUT SHANNON’S LATEST APPEARANCES!Learn more here.
Copyright 2001-2020 Shannon Elise-Muir Broden DBA Shannon Muir.
Follow MeFOLLOW SHANNON MUIR ON GOODREADS! Goodreads
SHANNON MUIR ON SNAPCHATFollow shannon.muir on Snapchat!
Contact UsEmailshannonmuirbooks@gmail.comFIND OUT MORE ABOUT SHANNON MUIR’S WRITINGAmazon Author Page
